{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648584457","data":{"timestamp":" 947648584457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__awe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648593777","data":{"timestamp":" 947648593777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ugo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648599683","data":{"timestamp":" 947648599682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ugo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648608090","data":{"timestamp":" 947648608090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ugo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648616590","data":{"timestamp":" 947648616590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ugo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648627673","data":{"timestamp":" 947648627673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__zizi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648634339","data":{"timestamp":" 947648634339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__zizi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648645788","data":{"timestamp":" 947648645787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__zito"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648654107","data":{"timestamp":" 947648654106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__zito"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648662358","data":{"timestamp":" 947648662358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__zito"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648672133","data":{"timestamp":" 947648672133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__iili"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648678109","data":{"timestamp":" 947648678109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__iili"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648691009","data":{"timestamp":" 947648691009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__iili"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648700526","data":{"timestamp":" 947648700526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__iili"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648719302","data":{"timestamp":" 947648719302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__etro"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648726122","data":{"timestamp":" 947648726122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__etro"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648735186","data":{"timestamp":" 947648735186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__etro"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648748936","data":{"timestamp":" 947648748936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eri"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648753416","data":{"timestamp":" 947648753416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write__eri"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648772252","data":{"timestamp":" 947648772252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_064234"," gameId":" 0548bd03-dadb-4e85-9d8b-f4acadd2492d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.2.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write__eri"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}